# **Darwood Antoine**

Brockton, MA (857)-251-9180

<u>darwooda@gmail.com</u> | <u>https://github.com/kidwizard42</u> | <u>https://kidwizard42.github.io/Portfolio/</u> | www.linkedin.com/in/darwoodantoine

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS:**

**Programming Languages:** Java | JavaScript | Python | Node JS | HTML | CSS **Programming Frameworks:** React | Spring | Django | Express Js | Mongoose

Databases: MongoDB | PostgreSQL

# **SELECT DEVELOPMENT EXPERIENCE:**

Arc Arcade: April 2022

Developed an arcade site with Java/Spring Boot, React, and Node JS. The site has online multiplayer Tic-tac-toe and another game that posts top scores on a leaderboard. It also contains instant chat messaging and a full CRUD section for posts.

Mini Trello Clone: March 2022

Worked in a team of three to develop a CRUD "to-do" app made with Django on the back end and React on the front end. User auth is handled using Django. Contains instant chat messaging from socket.io (made with node JS). Each user can manipulate a global to do list but also can create multiple of their own that only they can manipulate.

Social Media Site: February 2022

Collaborated with another student to create a CRUD social media site that allows users to log in and post and like/dislike posts. Users can only edit their posts and only get one like or dislike per post. The site has sessions authorization for security. Made with react, express, mongoose, mongo and MUI.

Pokémon Search Page: May 2021

Developed a webpage that uses the PokeApi API to request multiple pieces of information for specific Pokémon. Contains a random generator and a search function created using HTML, CSS, JS (DOM, API).

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

Software Engineering Apprentice: General Assembly, Remote

January 2021 – April 2022

A 12-week 420+ hour immersive program focusing on software engineering and implementing computer science fundamentals. Built responsive full stack applications in numerous languages and stacks using both relational and nonrelational databases.

Front Desk Manager: McGarr Security, Boston, MA

June 2018 - January 2022

- Assisted visitors and employees upon arrival and departure to GBH building
- Conducted building patrols to ensure safety standards and security of the facility
- Assisted employees with various safety and security needs and cleaners with miscellaneous tasks such as office lock outs, and escorting individuals to their car.

## **EDUCATION:**

General Assembly: Online

Software Engineering Immersion Program January 2022 – April 2022

**Udemy Developer Bootcamp:** Online

Full stack developer course March 2021

Newbury College: Brookline, MA

Bachelor of Science in Sport Management May 2018